<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<helpsectionsexport exported="1190903772">
	<helpsectionsgroup>
		<helpsections>
			<key>dashboard_dashboard_</key>
			<title>ACP Help System</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[<b>Welcome to the ACP Help System</b>
<br />This system will provide more advanced information on specific settings and pages in your Admin Control Panel.
<br />For pages that hold more information, you will see a box just like this one. 
<br />For individual settings, an image will appear next to them, which you can click for more information. The image will appear as: <img src="{skin_url}/images/about.png" alt="!" style="float:none;" />
<br />
<br />You can minimize each box by using the minimize icon in the top right of each box. To turn these help boxes off:
<br /><a href="{base_url}&section=tools&act=op&search=acp+help+system&code=setting_view">Click here</a> to be sent to the settings page for this.
<br />Alternatively you can simply navigate to the <i>Tools & Settings</i> tab, click on <i>General Configuration</i>, and then set <i>ACP Help System</i> to <i>No</i>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>tools_postoffice_mail_new</key>
			<title>Sending Bulk Emails</title>
			<helptext>When you send an email, a task on the board is triggered to send a certain amount of emails at once. Please note that in order for these tasks to run there must be activity the board itself. If you notice the Post Office is not sending your emails, please browse your board and actively browse for around 10 or so minutes. This should trigger the tasks needed to send the emails.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_sql_backup</key>
			<title>What settings should I pick?</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[<b>Simple Backup</b><br />
This function compiles a single back up file and prompts a browser dialogue box for you to save the file. This can only be used on small databases<br />
Normally the best results come from leaving the settings how they are. If you do experience issues, you may want to skip the non-essential data and enabling GZIP.<br />
Larger databases may time out using this tool. If this happens for you, please contact your webhost. They should be able to provide you with a backup. If you have SSH access to your site, our <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=kb">Knowledge Base</a> provides manual backup instructions using SSH.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_forum_new</key>
			<title>Permission Settings</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[When creating a <b>New Forum</b>, be sure to select which groups you want to be able to see the forum, post in the forum, and upload/download attachments. It will be at the bottom of this page. Without doing this, no one will be able to see the forum - not even admins.<br />
When creating a <b>New Category</b>, you only need to select who you want to be able to see the category.
]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_forum_donew</key>
			<title>Permission Settings</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[When creating a <b>New Forum</b>, be sure to select which groups you want to be able to see the forum, post in the forum, and upload/download attachments. It will be at the bottom of this page. Without doing this, no one will be able to see the forum - not even admins.<br />
When creating a <b>New Category</b>, you only need to select who you want to be able to see the category.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_forum_</key>
			<title>Managing your existing forums</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[When you need to <b>Edit Settings</b>, change permissions, or delete an existing forum/category, this can be done using the drop-down menu directly to the right of the forum or category. This is useful when changing who can see the forum and who can't.<br />
To add, remove, or edit a <b>Moderator</b> for a specific forum, simply click the tab on top of the forum list entitled <i>Show Moderator Options</i>. Existing moderators will be shown below their designated forums. To add a new one, click the checkbox to the right of the forum, scroll to the bottom of the page, and enter their name in <i>Add a moderator to all checked forum(s)</i>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_mem_search</key>
			<title><![CDATA[Finding & Pruning Members]]></title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[You can <b>Search</b> for a member on your forum from here. Just enter any or none of the fields to bring up the results. On the next page you can edit their account by clicking the drop-down next to their name.<br />
To <b>Prune / Mass Delete</b> members, simply select <i>Find Members to Prune (Mass Delete)</i> for the field <i>Type of Search</i>. You will also need to select some restrictions on who to prune, so fill in the other fields as desired.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_mem_changepassword</key>
			<title><![CDATA[Password Salt & Login Key]]></title>
			<helptext>In most cases, you can leave these two settings how they are. These are just unique member settings held in the database used for logging in.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_mtools_mod</key>
			<title>Manage User Registration/Email Change Queues</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This section will allow you to approve any members awaiting validation. Next to their name it will show if they are waiting <a href="{base_url}&section=tools&act=op&search=New+registration+email+validation?&code=setting_view">Admin Validation</a>, <a href="{base_url}&section=tools&act=op&search=New+registration+email+validation?&code=setting_view">Email Validation</a>, <a href="{base_url}&section=tools&act=op&code=findsetting&key=coppa">COPPA Validation</a>, or if they are awaiting an Email Change validation email.<br /><br />
You can approve or deny registrations by using the checkboxes to the right of their name, and the drop-down menu at the bottom of the list.<br /><br />
If users are having trouble receiving their validation emails, you can re-send them from this page using the same drop-down menu as used for approving or denying members.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>components_copyright_show</key>
			<title>Copyright Removal</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[<b>Please Note</b>: This is <u>not</u> the same as the IPB License Key. The Copyright Removal is a separate license that must be purchased.<br />
<br />
<b>To purchase</b> this license, please <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=contact">contact our sales department</a>.<br />
If you are <b>having issues</b> adding the Copyright Removal license, please <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=support">create a new support ticket</a>. Ensure that you include your board URL, access to a ROOT Admin account to your board, and the key you are trying to use.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_sets_</key>
			<title>Managing Skin Sets</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[On this page you will be able to see and alter all of your skins. To edit the skin directly, please click the drop-down to the right of each skin. If you wish to create a new unedited default skin, you can do this by clicking the dropdown menu to the right of <i>Skin Sets</i>. Here is a quick legend of some of the images on this page:<br />
<img src="{skin_url}/images/skin_default.gif" alt="Defaul Skin" style="float:none;" /> - This image indicates what skin is set as the board default. You can click this image on another skin to make it the default.<br />
<img src="{skin_url}/images/skin_visible.gif" alt="Visible Skin" style="float:none;" /> - This image indicates if the skin is visible or not. You can hide a skin by clicking this image next to it.<br />
<img src="{skin_url}/images/skin_forums.gif" alt="Forum Skin" style="float:none;" /> - This image indicates that the skin has been added to specific forums.
]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_support_support</key>
			<title>Submit Support Ticket</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[If you are experiencing an issue with your Invision Power Services software and require official assistance or support, you may utilize our ticketing system to submit a ticket. Please allow 24-48 hours for a response during normal business hours.<br/>
<br />
You must have an active support contract with us in order to submit a ticket.<br />
<br />
<b>NOTE - Internet Explorer users</b>: In some cases, Internet Explorer doesn't allow logging into an external site from a frame. If you are having trouble logging in, please visit the Client Area directly.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>components_helptext_new</key>
			<title>Internal Help Key</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[settinggoup_----- = Setting Group<br>
section_act_code = ACP page<br>
section_act_ = splash page<br>
conf_key = Setting
<br /><br />
a href="#" onclick='opener.ipsclass.location_jump("", 1); return false;'>]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_group_permsplash</key>
			<title>Forum Permission Management</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This section allows you to manage the permissions sets on your forum. You can click the drop-down menu to the right of the set, and edit it to select which forums they can see, post in, etc.<br />
<br />
<b>Used by Groups</b> relates to the member groups that use this set of permissions.
<b>Used by Members</b> relates to the number of members that are using this set of permissions rather than the set of permissions assigned to their group.
<b>Preview</b> the forums this set of permissions would provide access to in a quick, convenient format.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_multimod_</key>
			<title>Topic Multi-Moderation</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[With multi-moderation, you can combine multiple moderator actions into one easy shortcut. For example if your forum doesn't allow advertisement topics, you can create one for advertisement/spam messages. You can have a single moderator option to close the topic and add a stock reply to it. The possibilities are really open to what your specific needs are.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_multimod_new</key>
			<title>Topic Multi-Moderation</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[With multi-moderation, you can combine multiple moderator actions into one easy shortcut. For example if your forum doesn't allow advertisement topics, you can create one for advertisement/spam messages. You can have a single moderator option to close the topic and add a stock reply to it. The possibilities are really open to what your specific needs are.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_mem_add</key>
			<title>Creating a New User</title>
			<helptext>Registering users through the Admin CP is especially useful when creating new admin accounts. This will let you register accounts for users without having to go through the normal registration process, and bypassing any validation enabled.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_mem_title</key>
			<title>Setting up Member Ranking</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Ranks are images that show below a user's name on the forum.<br />
This section allows you to modify, delete, or add extra ranks. You can select the number of pip (images) to show for each rank. Alternatively, you can have it show a custom image instead of the pip images. Note, these custom images must reside in the '/style_images/{img_dir}/folder_team_icons' directory of your installation.
]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>components_gallery_show</key>
			<title>IP.Gallery</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This is a separate product designed to plug directly into your IP.Board. It offers your users an option to upload images to a gallery, as well as create their own albums. To purchase, please contact our <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=contact">Sales Team</a>. If you have already purchased this product and would like IPS to install it for you, please create a new <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=support">Support Ticket</a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>components_blog_show</key>
			<title>IP.Blog</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This is a separate product designed to plug directly into your IP.Board. It offers your users an option to create a personal Blog (web log) on your forum. This is similar to an online diary or journal. To purchase, please contact our <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=contact">Sales Team</a>. If you have already purchased this product and would like IPS to install it for you, please create a new <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=support">Support Ticket</a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>components_chatpara_show</key>
			<title>ParaChat Configuration</title>
			<helptext>ParaChat is a chat system that integrates into your board. It is offered by a third-party company. You can view information about this company in the frame below. If you have purchased this chat from them, you can enter the information they provided you into the box just below this help box.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>components_chatsigma_show</key>
			<title>AddOnChat Configuration</title>
			<helptext>AddOnChat is a chat system that integrates into your board. It is offered by a third-party company. You can view information about this company in the frame below. If you have purchased this chat from them, you can enter the information they provided you into the box just below this help box.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_support_</key>
			<title>Submit Support Ticket</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[If you are experiencing an issue with your Invision Power Services software and require official assistance or support, you may utilize our ticketing system to submit a ticket. Please allow 24-48 hours for a response during normal business hours.<br/>
<br />
You must have an active support contract with us in order to submit a ticket.<br />
<br />
<b>NOTE - Internet Explorer users</b>: In some cases, Internet Explorer doesn't allow logging into an external site from a frame. If you are having trouble logging in, please visit the Client Area directly.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_support_kb</key>
			<title>Knowledge Base</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[In the Knowledge Base you can find answers to common questions, patches for known issues, and other useful tutorials.
<br />
<br />
<b>NOTE - Internet Explorer users</b>: In some cases, Internet Explorer doesn't allow logging into an external site from a frame. If you are having trouble logging in, please visit the Client Area directly.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_support_bugs</key>
			<title>Bug Reports</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[You may submit and track all bugs reported to us by our users for Invision Power Board in the Bug Tracker below. This is <i>not</i> for support issues, but rather flaws in the software itself.
<br />
<br />
<b>NOTE - Internet Explorer users</b>: In some cases, Internet Explorer doesn't allow logging into an external site from a frame. If you are having trouble logging in, please visit the Bug Tracker directly.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_support_features</key>
			<title>Suggest Features</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[If you would like to request a feature, or see if a particular feature has already been requested, for Invision Power Services products this forum is the place to do so.
<br />
<br />
<b>NOTE - Internet Explorer users</b>: In some cases, Internet Explorer doesn't allow logging into an external site from a frame. If you are having trouble logging in, please visit the Feature Suggestions Forum directly.
]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_support_ipsbeyond</key>
			<title>IPSBeyond.com - Official Resource Site</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[IPSBeyond is a customer-only resource site where you can find helpful articles, modifications, skins, and customer-to-customer support. Note that all content and advice found on IPS Beyond is provided as-is by the individual user, and is not endorsed nor support by Invision Power Services, Inc. If you are just looking to chat or would like to look for additional resources for your board, this is the first place to go.<br />
<br/>
You must first register an account in your client area home page in order to access IPSBeyond.
<br />
<br />
<b>NOTE - Internet Explorer users</b>: In some cases, Internet Explorer doesn't allow logging into an external site from a frame. If you are having trouble logging in, please visit the IPSBeyond.com directly.
]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_support_doctor</key>
			<title>IP.Board Documentation</title>
			<helptext>You can download the IP.Board Documentation on this page. It will cover the usage of this board from the user-side as well as the admin-side. For skin and modification authors, we also offer a full CSS guide and Developer Documentaiton.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_support_contact</key>
			<title>Contact IPS</title>
			<helptext>If you would like to contact us you can find our current contact information and hours of operation below.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_mem_</key>
			<title><![CDATA[Finding & Pruning Members]]></title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[You can <b>Search</b> for a member on your forum from here. Just enter any or none of the fields to bring up the results. On the next page you can edit their account by clicking the drop-down next to their name.<br />
To <b>Prune / Mass Delete</b> members, simply select <i>Find Members to Prune (Mass Delete)</i> for the field <i>Type of Search</i>. You will also need to select some restrictions on who to prune, so fill in the other fields as desired.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_group_</key>
			<title>User Groups</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[User Grouping is a quick and powerful way to organize your members. There are 4 preset groups that you cannot remove (Validating, Guest, Member and Admin) although you may edit these at will. A good example of user grouping is to set up a group called 'Moderators' and allow them access to certain forums other groups do not have access to.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_mtools_lock</key>
			<title>Managing Locked User Accounts</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This section allows you to see which member accounts are currently locked. It also allows you a way to manually unlock these accounts. An account will become locked after the same IP address fails to log into it after a certain amount of time.<br />
You can manage these settings by <a href="{base_url}&section=tools&act=op&search=locked&code=setting_view">clicking here</a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_field_add</key>
			<title><![CDATA[Tip regarding "Expected Input Format"]]></title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[If you enter <b>n</b>, for example, the user will only be able to enter <i>one</i> number. This limits the amount of information they can enter. So as an example, if you wanted a (5 character) 'Zip Code' field, you would put the expected input format as: <b>nnnnn</b><br/>
Anything besides 5 numbers would be rejected. They would not be able to enter more or less numbers either.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_field_</key>
			<title>Adding Custom Profile Fields</title>
			<helptext>Custom Profile fields can be used to add optional or required fields to be completed when registering or editing a profile. This is useful if you wish to record data from your members that is not already present in the default board.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_forum_empty</key>
			<title>Emptying a Forum</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[<b>THIS WILL DELETE ALL TOPICS, POSTS AND POLLS. THERE IS <u>NO</u> UNDO.</b><br />
The forum itself will not be deleted - please ensure you wish to carry out this action before continuing.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_forum_skinedit</key>
			<title>Assigning a Specific Skin to a Forum</title>
			<helptext>You may choose to either add or remove a skin set to this forum. When you select a skin, it will also show on this forum, no matter what the user has set as their skin choice.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_forum_frules</key>
			<title>Forum Specific Rules</title>
			<helptext>On this page, you can enter the rules for a specific forum. They can be shown as a link or shown directly on the forum page. They will be seen anytime someone is in this forum, as well as starting/replying to topics in this forum.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_forum_pedit</key>
			<title>Forum Access Permissions</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Check the box for access, uncheck to not allow access.<br />
If you deny show access for a permission set, they will not see the forum.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_forum_edit</key>
			<title>Editing Settings of a Forum</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This section will allow you to edit an existing forum. If you wish to adjust the forum permissions (who has the ability to start, reply and read topics) click on 'Edit Permissions' on the <i>Manage Forums</i> page.<br />
On this page you can enable posting moderation, topic ratings, polls, HTML, and many other features of the forum.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_diag_</key>
			<title>IP.Board Diagnostics Tools</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[<b>Please note that these tools are moderately resource intensive - allow some time for them to run.</b><br />
You are currently on the System Overview page. A quick overview of your server will be provided here, including your SQL and PHP versions, as well as other essential data. You can also view your IP.Board upgrade history at the bottom of this page.<br /><br />
If you are experiencing <b>IPS Driver Errors</b>, please run the <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=diag&code=dbchecker" onclick="xmlobj = new ajax_request();xmlobj.show_loading()">Database Checker</a>, to see if you are missing any database structure. If you are experiencing <b>forum slowness</b>, ensure your <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=diag&code=dbindex" onclick="xmlobj = new ajax_request();xmlobj.show_loading()">database indexes</a> are added properly. If you are having issues with <b>uploading</b> to the forum, please check your <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=diag&code=filepermissions" onclick="xmlobj = new ajax_request();xmlobj.show_loading()">file permissions</a>. Finally, if you are having issues with <b>blank pages</b>, please ensure none of your files have <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=diag&code=whitespace" onclick="xmlobj = new ajax_request();xmlobj.show_loading()">whitespace</a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_diag_dbchecker</key>
			<title>Database Structure Check</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[If you are missing necessary database tables, or columns in those database tables, you will see database errors (commonly shown as <b>IPS Driver Error</b>) or missing data when browsing IPB. Please use the links or queries provided below to remedy any missing columns or tables.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_diag_dbindex</key>
			<title>Database Index Check</title>
			<helptext>Database indexes help your database engine work more efficiently with the data it hosts. If any of the indexes are missing, it can cause your site to run slower than it should. Please use the appropriate links or queries to fix any indexes reported missing below.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_diag_filepermissions</key>
			<title>File Permission Check</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[When the permissions for your files or folders are wrong, it can cause issues such as your attachments, skins, and emoticons not uploading correctly.<br />
Certain files and directories must have the proper permissions set on them in order for IP.Board to properly write data to your disk. On Windows, you should ensure the files have "Read/Write" permissions, while on Unix/Linux you should ensure the files are "CHMOD 777".]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_diag_whitespace</key>
			<title>Whitespace Check</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[If there is any whitespace before or after the PHP tags in files used by IP.Board, it can result in blank pages or malformed HTML. If any results are returned you should open those files and delete the extra spaces or line breaks at the beginning and/or end of the file.<br />
<br />
The starting PHP tag is:<br />
<b>&lt;?php</b> or <b>&lt;?</b><br />
<br />
The ending PHP tag is:<br />
<b>?&gt;</b>]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_sql_</key>
			<title>Managing Your Database</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[In this section you can manage your database. For most beginners, this section is of little use unless there is an <b>IPS Driver Error</b>. If you are encountering such an error, please check the "Rows" column in this section. If you see any of the row without a number whatsoever, please check the checkmark next to that database table. At the bottom, use the drop-down menu and select "Repair Selected Tables."<br />
If you continue to get <b>IPS Driver Errors</b>, please run the <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=diag&code=dbchecker" onclick="xmlobj = new ajax_request();xmlobj.show_loading()">Database Checker</a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_stats_reg</key>
			<title>Registration Statistics</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The Statistics Center allows you to view the stats of your forum, ranging from number of number of PMs to number of Topic Views, and so on.
<br />
Note: The statistics generated are based on the information currently held in the database, they do not take into account pruned forums or delete posts, etc.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_stats_topic</key>
			<title>Topic Statistics</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The Statistics Center allows you to view the stats of your forum, ranging from number of number of PMs to number of Topic Views, and so on.
<br />
Note: The statistics generated are based on the information currently held in the database, they do not take into account pruned forums or delete posts, etc.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_stats_post</key>
			<title>Posts Statistics</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The Statistics Center allows you to view the stats of your forum, ranging from number of number of PMs to number of Topic Views, and so on.
<br />
Note: The statistics generated are based on the information currently held in the database, they do not take into account pruned forums or delete posts, etc.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_stats_msg</key>
			<title>Personal Message Statistics</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The Statistics Center allows you to view the stats of your forum, ranging from number of number of PMs to number of Topic Views, and so on.
<br />
Note: The statistics generated are based on the information currently held in the database, they do not take into account pruned forums or delete posts, etc.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_stats_views</key>
			<title>Topic View Statistics</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The Statistics Center allows you to view the stats of your forum, ranging from number of number of PMs to number of Topic Views, and so on.
<br />
Note: The statistics generated are based on the information currently held in the database, they do not take into account pruned forums or delete posts, etc.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_components_</key>
			<title>Managing Your Components</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[All installed components will be shown on this page. To quickly disable or enable a specific component, click the image in the "Enabled" column.<br /><br />
<img src="{skin_url}/images/aff_tick.png" alt="Green Checkmark" style="float:none;" /> - This image means the component is currently enabled on your IP.Board. Clicking it will change it to the image below.<br />
<img src="{skin_url}/images/aff_cross.png" alt="Red X" style="float:none;" /> - This image means the component is currently disabled on your IP.Board. Clicking it will change it to the image above.<br /><br />
To change the settings for your components, please visit the <a href="{base_url}&section=components">Components</a> tab.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_emaillog_</key>
			<title>Member-to-Member Email Logs</title>
			<helptext>All emails sent from members are recorded here. This does not store bulk emails, subscription emails, or any other emails sent from the board itself.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_adminlog_</key>
			<title>Admin Log Manager</title>
			<helptext>You may view and remove actions performed by your administrators in mission critical areas of the Admin CP (such as forum control, member control, group control, help files, and moderator log management). Note this does not log setting changes.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_emailerror_</key>
			<title>Email Error Logs</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[When the board encounters an error sending the email, it will be logged here for investigation. If all of the board emails are encountering errors, please ensure your <a href="{base_url}&section=tools&act=op&code=findsetting&key=emailset-up">email settings</a> are correct.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_spiderlog_</key>
			<title>Search Engine Spider Logs</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[If your IP.Board is visited by Search Engine Spiders that index your site, their visits will be logged here. Please note that this section may get very large and take up a lot of space. It is highly recommended to setup <a href="{base_url}&section=tools&act=op&code=findsetting&key=log_prune">Log Pruning</a> to help this.<br />
To setup which spiders are logged, please visit the <a href="{base_url}&section=tools&act=op&code=findsetting&key=searchenginespiders">Search Engine Spiders</a> configuration page.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_warnlog_</key>
			<title>Warn Logs</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[If you have the <a href="{base_url}&section=tools&act=op&code=findsetting&key=warnsetup">Warning System</a> setup, this will log any warnings given to members. Please note that removing the log does not reduce the warning level of that specific member.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_loginlog_</key>
			<title>Admin Login Logs</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This will show you every attempt made to log into your Admin CP. It will show you if the login is successful or not under the "Status" column. If you notice an unrecognized IP repeatedly trying to login, it is recommended to add this IP to your <a href="{base_url}&section=content&act=babw&code=ban">Ban Filters</a>.<br />You can also set it up so that if an IP fails to login after a certain amount of tries, they will be locked out. These settings can be found by <a href="{base_url}&section=tools&act=op&search=locked&code=setting_view">clicking here</a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_security_</key>
			<title>Security Enhancements</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[While all of these tools are optional, it is <b><font color="red">highly</font></b> recommended to read through each one carefully and make any changes where needed. If you are unsure of what a certain feature does, please view our <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=doctor">Documentation</a>. If you still have questions, please feel free to create a new <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=support">support ticket</a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_security_list_admins</key>
			<title>Members with ACP Access</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Please review everyone on this list. If you see anyone that you don't recognize or that shouldn't have access to your Admin CP, please remove them immediately. You can remove them by using the "Edit" link next to their name.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>admin_acpperms_acpp_list</key>
			<title>Admin CP Restrictions</title>
			<helptext>If you have members who can access the Admin CP, but are not placed in the Root Admin group, you can limit what they can do and see inside the Admin CP. Simply search for the member you want to restrict by clicking the drop-down menu below.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_msubs_index-gateways</key>
			<title>Subscription Manager - Payment Gateways</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Payment Gateways are services that allow you to collect money from users based off subscriptions. In order to use a gateway, you must have an account with the specific company. For example, if you wish to use PayPal, you must have an account on the <a href="https://www.paypal.com" target="_blank">PayPal website</a>.<br />
To setup a gateway, click the drop-down to the right of the gateway, and select <i>Set Up Payment Gateway...</i>]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_msubs_editmethod</key>
			<title>Subscription Manager - Editing a Gateway</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This page is used to configure the payment gateway information. If you are unsure of any of this information, such as <i>Seller ID</i>, <i>Gateway Associated Email Address</i>, <i>etc.</i>, please contact this specific gateway provider, and they can supply you with the information needed.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_msubs_index-packages</key>
			<title>Subscription Manager - Managing Your Packages</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[A package is what the user will subscribe to. Common setups for this include:<br />
Setting up a recurring package every month that promotes users to another group. This is useful if you wish to allow paying members access to separate sections of the board.<br />
Setting up a <i>Donator</i> type group that never expires. This will allow people who provide money to your board to be placed in a specially selected group.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_msubs_currency</key>
			<title>Subscription Manager - Currency Manager</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[<b>Currency Information</b><br />
The currency you set as default becomes the currency the subscriptions are based in. For example, if you chose USD as default, entering a value of 1.00 for a subscription package means that the subscription package costs 1.00 USD. If you choose another default you may want to edit all the subscription values as they will become incorrect. Also if you choose another default, you will also want to edit the exchange values.<br />
<br />
For up-to-date currency conversion, visit <a href="http://www.xe.com" target="_blank">XE.com</a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_msubs_addtransaction</key>
			<title>Subscription Manager - Manually Add Transaction</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Using this section, you can manually add a transaction for a user. Please note that if this is done, this user will not have to pay for the transaction, but will have the privileges of anyone who has paid.<br />
<b>Note</b>: If you wish to have this user revert back to their previous group after the subscription ends, be sure to put their <u>current</u> under <i>Previous Group</i>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_msubs_install-index</key>
			<title>Subscription Manager - Adding a New Gateway</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[<b>Note</b>: This section is mostly for advanced users who are familiar with PHP and coding custom modules.<br />
To install a new payment gateway module, simply upload the file 'class_gw_{name}.php' into '/sources/classes/paymentgateways' and then click on the 'install' link. Modules showing as 'installed' are active and can be set up from within the '<i>Manage Payment Gateways</i>' link.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_calendars_calendar_list</key>
			<title>Applying Permissions to a Calendar</title>
			<helptext>Using the drop-down to the right of each calendar, you can edit the settings for it. On this page you will have the option to select which groups can create new events, see events, and so on. It is important to set this information, or no one will be able to use your calendar.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_babw_badword</key>
			<title>Using Badword Filters</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The badword filter allows you to globally replace words from a members post, signature and topic title. You can add/edit and remove bad word filters in this section. As a note, by default the Admin group can bypass the badword list. You can change this by editing this group on the <a href="{base_url}&section=content&act=group">Manage User Groups</a> page.<br />
<br />
<b>Loose matching</b>: If you entered 'hell' as a bad word, it will replace 'hell' and 'hello' with either your replacement if entered or 6 hashes (case insensitive).<br />
<b>Exact matching</b>: If you entered 'hell' as a bad word, it will replace 'hell' only with either your replacement if entered or 6 hashes (case insensitive).<br />
<b>Import a Badword List</b>: You can use this if you have a pre-made badword list XML file. An example one is available in our <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=kb">Knowledge Base</a>. Simply search for <i>badword</i>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_babw_ban</key>
			<title>Banning Members</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[To ban an existing member, simply go to the <a href="{base_url}&section=content&act=mem&code=search">Manage Members</a> page, find and edit their account, and finally switch their Primary User Group to <i>Banned</i>. This will stop them from viewing the board when logged in. To ban certain IPs from viewing the board, or to ban certain emails or username names from signing up, you can use this section.<br />
<br />
<b>Note</b>: You can use * as a wildcard in any Username, IP, or Email filter. (Example: 127.0.*, *@yahoo.com, bannedname*). Also ensure there are no spaces before or after your ban filter - in some cases this will cause the filter to not work properly.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_attach_types</key>
			<title>Adding New Attachment Types</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[On this page you can alter existing attachment types and add new ones. To add a new one, use the 'Add New Attachment Type' button at the bottom of the page. This is useful if your board is geared towards a specific subject where non-standard attachments need to be uploaded.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_attach_attach_add</key>
			<title>Attachment Mini-Image</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This image will need to be stored in:<br />
/style_images/<i>{imgdir}</i>/folder_mime_types/<br/><br/>
For example, the information you would enter would be: <i>folder_mime_types/music.gif</i><br />
Be sure this image is uploaded for each one of your custom image sets.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_mem_changename</key>
			<title>Changing a Login Name</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Please note that this is the name the user will login with. This does not change the name that is displayed on the board. To change that, select the <i>Edit Member's Display Name...</i> from the drop-down menu on the previous page.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_mem_change_display_name</key>
			<title>Changing a Display Name</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Please note this is the name the user is shown as. This does not change the name they login with. To change that, select the <i>Edit Member's Log In User Name...</i> from the drop-down menu on the previous page.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_mem_banmember</key>
			<title>Suspending a Member</title>
			<helptext>The suspension system is an automated temporary ban. Simply choose the duration of the suspension and submit the form below. It will suspend this member for the amount of time given, and automatically unsuspend them when that time is up.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_mem_deleteposts</key>
			<title>Deleting Member Posts / Topics</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[<b>Note</b>: There is <b><u><i>NO</i></u></b>  undo for this. If you run this, all of the posts and topics from the members will be lost. If you have a <a href="{base_url}&section=tools&act=op&code=findsetting&key=trashcanset-up">Trash Can Forum</a> setup, you can select the <i>Use Trash Can?</i> option to move them there.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_calendars_calendar_add</key>
			<title>Calendar Permissions</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Please ensure that the <i>Calendar Permissions</i> of this section are filled out. Otherwise no one will be able to see this calendar - not even you.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_group_add</key>
			<title>Creating a New Group</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Most of the time when a new group is created, separate permissions for this group are wanted. If this is the case for you, please first create a new permission set on the <a href="{base_url}&section=content&act=group&code=permsplash">Manage Permissions</a> page. Once you have created a new permission set for this group, come back to this page and for the option <i>'Use which permission sets...'</i>, select the newly created permission set. Now when you go to edit your forum permissions, your new group/set will appear.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_group_dopermadd</key>
			<title>Create a New User Group?</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Since you have just created a new permission set, if you wish to create a new user group to use this set, simply go to the <a href="{base_url}&section=content&act=group&code=add">Manage User Groups</a> section.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>dashboard_dashboard_login-complete</key>
			<title>ACP Help System</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[<b>Welcome to the ACP Help System</b>
<br />This system will provide more advanced information on specific settings and pages in your Admin Control Panel.
<br />For pages that hold more information, you will see a box just like this one. 
<br />For individual settings, an image will appear next to them, which you can click for more information. The image will appear as: <img src="{skin_url}/images/about.png" alt="!" style="float:none;" />
<br />
<br />You can minimize each box by using the minimize icon in the top right of each box. To turn these help boxes off:
<br /><a href="{base_url}&section=tools&act=op&search=acp+help+system&code=setting_view">Click here</a> to be sent to the settings page for this.
<br />Alternatively you can simply navigate to the <i>Tools & Settings</i> tab, click on <i>General Configuration</i>, and then set <i>ACP Help System</i> to <i>No</i>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_wrap_edit</key>
			<title>Editing the Board Header and Footer Wrapper</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This section controls the basic layout of your board. You will be able to move certain sections around in this section. For example if you wanted, you could move the member bar above the board header, etc.<br />
Editing this will copy the changes to any children skins of this set.<br /><br />
If you would like assistance with custom skin changes, it is recommended to visit our official resource site <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=ipsbeyond">IPSBeyond.com</a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_templ_template-sections-list</key>
			<title>Editing Your Templates</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This section will provide you a way of editing the template HTML. This is useful if you want to tweak a certain section of your board. The templates use standard HTML formatting in most areas. Templates are seperated by where they appear on the board -- For example, the board header is in the 'All Global HTML' section, while the code for topics is held in the 'Topic View' area, and so on.
<br /><br />
If you would like assistance with custom skin changes, it is recommended to visit our official resource site <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=ipsbeyond">IPSBeyond.com</a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_style_edit</key>
			<title>Edit the CSS (Stylesheet) Colors</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The CSS (Stylesheet) controls the colors and appearance of your board. Using this form, you can edit the way your board looks.
<br /><br /><b>Need help?</b> View the <a href="{skin_url}/colours.html" target="_blank"><b>Online Color Picker</b></a> for help with the color codes. A full CSS/colors guide is available on our <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=doctor"><b>Documentation</b></a> page.
If you would like assistance with custom skin changes, it is recommended to visit our official resource site <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=ipsbeyond"><b>IPSBeyond.com</b></a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_style_colouredit</key>
			<title>Edit the CSS (Stylesheet) Colors</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The CSS (Stylesheet) controls the colors and appearance of your board. Using this form, you can edit the way your board looks.
<br /><br /><b>Need help?</b> View the <a href="{skin_url}/colours.html" target="_blank"><b>Online Color Picker</b></a> for help with the color codes. A full CSS/colors guide is available on our <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=doctor"><b>Documentation</b></a> page.
If you would like assistance with custom skin changes, it is recommended to visit our official resource site <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=ipsbeyond"><b>IPSBeyond.com</b></a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_import_</key>
			<title><![CDATA[Exporting & Importing]]></title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[On this page you can create a backup of your current skin and import new skins to your board.<br /><br />
<b>Exporting...</b> The skin set is comprised of two separate XML files - the Skin Template XML and the Images XML. Be sure to select both of these when exporting if you want to export your entire skin. Exporting is useful when backing up your skin.<br />
<b>Importing...</b> This where you import new skins. You can download new skins using a resource site such as <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=ipsbeyond">IPSBeyond.com</a>. When a skin has been downloaded, it will come with two files - one for the skin template and one for the images. Be sure to import both of these taking note to each field when importing, and adjusting accordingly.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_skindiff_</key>
			<title>Skin Template HTML Differences</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This tool is useful when comparing the changes made to one of your skin sets against that of the master default template. To run a differences report on an existing skin, please go to the <a href="{base_url}&section=lookandfeel&act=sets">Skin Manager</a>, and select <i>Generate Differences Report...</i> from the drop-down next to the skin. 
]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_skinremap_</key>
			<title>Skin Remapping</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This sections allows you to force a skin set to be used based off the URL someone is viewing. An <i>example</i> of usage is if you wish to make all profiles have use the same skin set:<br /><br />
For <b>Type</b> use <i>Contains</i>. This will look for any URL that contains your specified input. For <b>URL</b> enter <i>showuser</i> . Finally select the <b>Skin Set</b> to assign to this. Now whenever someone views a profile (which has "showuser" in the URL) it will show the skin you have selected.<br />
Note this is not limited to profiles - this tool can control any section of the forum you want. You just need to enter the URL of the page(s) you want to have a different skin.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_skinremap_remap_edit</key>
			<title>Skin Remapping</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This sections allows you to force a skin set to be used based off the URL someone is viewing. An <i>example</i> of usage is if you wish to make all profiles have use the same skin set:<br /><br />
For <b>Type</b> use <i>Contains</i>. This will look for any URL that contains your specified input. For <b>URL</b> enter <i>showuser</i> . Finally select the <b>Skin Set</b> to assign to this. Now whenever someone views a profile (which has "showuser" in the URL) it will show the skin you have selected.<br />
Note this is not limited to profiles - this tool can control any section of the forum you want. You just need to enter the URL of the page(s) you want to have a different skin.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_skinremap_remap_add</key>
			<title>Skin Remapping</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This sections allows you to force a skin set to be used based off the URL someone is viewing. An <i>example</i> of usage is if you wish to make all profiles have use the same skin set:<br /><br />
For <b>Type</b> use <i>Contains</i>. This will look for any URL that contains your specified input. For <b>URL</b> enter <i>showuser</i> . Finally select the <b>Skin Set</b> to assign to this. Now whenever someone views a profile (which has "showuser" in the URL) it will show the skin you have selected.<br />
Note this is not limited to profiles - this tool can control any section of the forum you want. You just need to enter the URL of the page(s) you want to have a different skin.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_babw_ban_add</key>
			<title>Banning Members</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[To ban an existing member, simply go to the <a href="{base_url}&section=content&act=mem&code=search">Manage Members</a> page, find and edit their account, and finally switch their Primary User Group to <i>Banned</i>. This will stop them from viewing the board when logged in. To ban certain IPs from viewing the board, or to ban certain emails or username names from signing up, you can use this section.<br />
<br />
<b>Note</b>: You can use * as a wildcard in any Username, IP, or Email filter. (Example: 127.0.*, *@yahoo.com, bannedname*). Also ensure there are no spaces before or after your ban filter - in some cases this will cause the filter to not work properly.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_babw_ban_delete</key>
			<title>Banning Members</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[To ban an existing member, simply go to the <a href="{base_url}&section=content&act=mem&code=search">Manage Members</a> page, find and edit their account, and finally switch their Primary User Group to <i>Banned</i>. This will stop them from viewing the board when logged in. To ban certain IPs from viewing the board, or to ban certain emails or username names from signing up, you can use this section.<br />
<br />
<b>Note</b>: You can use * as a wildcard in any Username, IP, or Email filter. (Example: 127.0.*, *@yahoo.com, bannedname*). Also ensure there are no spaces before or after your ban filter - in some cases this will cause the filter to not work properly.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_skintools_easylogo</key>
			<title>Changing Your Logo</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Using this tool, you can upload or link to a new logo for your skin. Be sure to select the skin you want to apply the logo to by using the drop-down menu next to <i>Apply to which skin set?</i>. Note that some custom third-party skins may not have the proper HTML to allow the logo to be changed. For assistance with these custom skins, it is recommended to contact the skin author.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_babw_badword_add</key>
			<title>Using Badword Filters</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The badword filter allows you to globally replace words from a members post, signature and topic title. You can add/edit and remove bad word filters in this section. As a note, by default the Admin group can bypass the badword list. You can change this by editing this group on the <a href="{base_url}&section=content&act=group">Manage User Groups</a> page.<br />
<br />
<b>Loose matching</b>: If you entered 'hell' as a bad word, it will replace 'hell' and 'hello' with either your replacement if entered or 6 hashes (case insensitive).<br />
<b>Exact matching</b>: If you entered 'hell' as a bad word, it will replace 'hell' only with either your replacement if entered or 6 hashes (case insensitive).<br />
<b>Import a Badword List</b>: You can use this if you have a pre-made badword list XML file. An example one is available in our <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=kb">Knowledge Base</a>. Simply search for <i>badword</i>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_babw_badword_remove</key>
			<title>Using Badword Filters</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The badword filter allows you to globally replace words from a members post, signature and topic title. You can add/edit and remove bad word filters in this section. As a note, by default the Admin group can bypass the badword list. You can change this by editing this group on the <a href="{base_url}&section=content&act=group">Manage User Groups</a> page.<br />
<br />
<b>Loose matching</b>: If you entered 'hell' as a bad word, it will replace 'hell' and 'hello' with either your replacement if entered or 6 hashes (case insensitive).<br />
<b>Exact matching</b>: If you entered 'hell' as a bad word, it will replace 'hell' only with either your replacement if entered or 6 hashes (case insensitive).<br />
<b>Import a Badword List</b>: You can use this if you have a pre-made badword list XML file. An example one is available in our <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=kb">Knowledge Base</a>. Simply search for <i>badword</i>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_lang_import</key>
			<title>Importing Language Packs</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Uploading new language packs is accomplished on this page. To obtain a pre-made language pack, it is recommended to visit our official resource site <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=ipsbeyond">IPSBeyond.com</a>. Once you have the XML file for the language pack downloaded, simply upload it through the form below. One it is added, you can click to <a href="{base_url}&section=lookandfeel&act=lang">Manage Your Languages</a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_lang_</key>
			<title><![CDATA[Managing & Editing Languages]]></title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The language system controls all of the text that is shown on your board as well as the text sent in board emails. This section allows you to view your currently installed skin sets, edit the language bits, see how many members are using the language, among other things. To <b>edit</b> a language, simply click the <i>Edit</i> link next to the language.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_lang_edit</key>
			<title>Editing Language Files</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Editing your language files is similiar to edit the skin HTML templates. Languages are grouped by how and where they display on the board. For example, to edit the text in the global header, you would edit the file <i>lang_global</i>. To edit the language sent in emails from the board, edit the file <i>lang_email_content</i>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>help_support_viewallbugs</key>
			<title>bfarber says:</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA["It was before me!"]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_emoticons_emo</key>
			<title>Emoticon Manager</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The emoticon manager lets you manage your emoticon folders, as well as upload new emoticons.<br />
To <b>edit</b> emoticons, click the name of the set you wish to edit. This will show all emoticons currently in that set.<br />
To <b>upload</b> new emoticons, be sure to click the checkbox next to each folder you want to upload the emoticon into, and then upload the emoticons using the forms at the bottom of the page. Note all emoticons will be copied to the 'default' folder as well as the folder selected.<br />
To <b>assign a set to a skin</b>, visit the <a href="{base_url}&section=lookandfeel&act=sets">Skin Manager</a> section. Next to the skin you wish to assign one to, click <i>Edit Settings</i>, and there will be an option to assign an emoticon set.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_emoticons_emo_upload</key>
			<title>Emoticon Manager</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The emoticon manager lets you manage your emoticon folders, as well as upload new emoticons.<br />
To <b>edit</b> emoticons, click the name of the set you wish to edit. This will show all emoticons currently in that set.<br />
To <b>upload</b> new emoticons, be sure to click the checkbox next to each folder you want to upload the emoticon into, and then upload the emoticons using the forms at the bottom of the page. Note all emoticons will be copied to the 'default' folder as well as the folder selected.<br />
To <b>assign a set to a skin</b>, visit the <a href="{base_url}&section=lookandfeel&act=sets">Skin Manager</a> section. Next to the skin you wish to assign one to, click <i>Edit Settings</i>, and there will be an option to assign an emoticon set.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_emoticons_emo_setadd</key>
			<title>Emoticon Manager</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The emoticon manager lets you manage your emoticon folders, as well as upload new emoticons.<br />
To <b>edit</b> emoticons, click the name of the set you wish to edit. This will show all emoticons currently in that set.<br />
To <b>upload</b> new emoticons, be sure to click the checkbox next to each folder you want to upload the emoticon into, and then upload the emoticons using the forms at the bottom of the page. Note all emoticons will be copied to the 'default' folder as well as the folder selected.<br />
To <b>assign a set to a skin</b>, visit the <a href="{base_url}&section=lookandfeel&act=sets">Skin Manager</a> section. Next to the skin you wish to assign one to, click <i>Edit Settings</i>, and there will be an option to assign an emoticon set.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_emoticons_emo_manage</key>
			<title>Editing Your Emoticons</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The most common format for emoticons is similar to:<br />
:namehere:<br />
<b>Note</b>: It is recommended to NOT include these special characters: ' , "<br />
This can cause the emoticon not to display properly.
<br /><br />
To make it so the emoticon will show up next to the editor when making a post, set it to <i>Clickable</i>. To add an unassigned emoticon to the set, check <i>Add</i> next to each one.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_emoticons_emo_setremove</key>
			<title>Emoticon Manager</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The emoticon manager lets you manage your emoticon folders, as well as upload new emoticons.<br />
To <b>edit</b> emoticons, click the name of the set you wish to edit. This will show all emoticons currently in that set.<br />
To <b>upload</b> new emoticons, be sure to click the checkbox next to each folder you want to upload the emoticon into, and then upload the emoticons using the forms at the bottom of the page. Note all emoticons will be copied to the 'default' folder as well as the folder selected.<br />
To <b>assign a set to a skin</b>, visit the <a href="{base_url}&section=lookandfeel&act=sets">Skin Manager</a> section. Next to the skin you wish to assign one to, click <i>Edit Settings</i>, and there will be an option to assign an emoticon set.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_emoticons_emo_setedit</key>
			<title>Emoticon Manager</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The emoticon manager lets you manage your emoticon folders, as well as upload new emoticons.<br />
To <b>edit</b> emoticons, click the name of the set you wish to edit. This will show all emoticons currently in that set.<br />
To <b>upload</b> new emoticons, be sure to click the checkbox next to each folder you want to upload the emoticon into, and then upload the emoticons using the forms at the bottom of the page. Note all emoticons will be copied to the 'default' folder as well as the folder selected.<br />
To <b>assign a set to a skin</b>, visit the <a href="{base_url}&section=lookandfeel&act=sets">Skin Manager</a> section. Next to the skin you wish to assign one to, click <i>Edit Settings</i>, and there will be an option to assign an emoticon set.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_emoticons_emo_doedit</key>
			<title>Editing Your Emoticons</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The most common format for emoticons is similiar to:<br />
:namehere:<br />
<b>Note</b>: It is recommended to NOT include these special characters: ' , "<br />
This can cause the emoticon not to display properly.
<br /><br />
To make it so the emoticon will show up next to the editor when making a post, set it to <i>Clickable</i>. To add an unassigned emoticon to the set, check <i>Add</i> next to each one.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_emoticons_emo_doadd</key>
			<title>Editing Your Emoticons</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The most common format for emoticons is similiar to:<br />
:namehere:<br />
<b>Note</b>: It is recommended to NOT include these special characters: ' , "<br />
This can cause the emoticon not to display properly.
<br /><br />
To make it so the emoticon will show up next to the editor when making a post, set it to <i>Clickable</i>. To add an unassigned emoticon to the set, check <i>Add</i> next to each one.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_emoticons_emo_packimport</key>
			<title>Emoticon Manager</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The emoticon manager lets you manage your emoticon folders, as well as upload new emoticons.<br />
To <b>edit</b> emoticons, click the name of the set you wish to edit. This will show all emoticons currently in that set.<br />
To <b>upload</b> new emoticons, be sure to click the checkbox next to each folder you want to upload the emoticon into, and then upload the emoticons using the forms at the bottom of the page. Note all emoticons will be copied to the 'default' folder as well as the folder selected.<br />
To <b>assign a set to a skin</b>, visit the <a href="{base_url}&section=lookandfeel&act=sets">Skin Manager</a> section. Next to the skin you wish to assign one to, click <i>Edit Settings</i>, and there will be an option to assign an emoticon set.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>lookandfeel_emoticons_emo_packsplash</key>
			<title><![CDATA[Exporting & Importing Emoticons]]></title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[<b>Exporting</b> emoticons allows you to create an XML file backup of your emoticons. It is useful if you wish to share your emoticon set with another board.<br />
<b>Importing</b> emoticon sets can be done on this page as well. Importing a full pack allows you to import a complete set at one time. To obtain pre-made emoticon packs, it is recommended to visit our official resource site <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=ipsbeyond">IPSBeyond.com</a>.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>tools_task_</key>
			<title>Task Manager</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The task manager contains scheduled tasks for your board. Please note that these tasks are run only when the board is accessed, so the 'Next Run' time is to be used as a guide only, as it depends on how often your board gets traffic.
<br /><br />Icon legend:</b><br />
<img src="{skin_url}/images/task_cron.gif" alt="Cron Setup" style="float:none;" /> - This image is for advanced users who wish to set up a cron job for the tasks. This is useful if the board is not accessed often, but you want the tasks to run exactly on time.<br />
<img src="{skin_url}/images/task_run.gif" alt="Run Now" style="float:none;" /> - If this image turns red, it means this task needs to be run. To run a task, simply click on this icon and it will run the selected task.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>tools_task_task_run_now</key>
			<title>Task Manager</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The task manager contains scheduled tasks for your board. Please note that these tasks are run only when the board is accessed, so the 'Next Run' time is to be used as a guide only, as it depends on how often your board gets traffic.
<br /><br />Icon legend:</b><br />
<img src="{skin_url}/images/task_cron.gif" alt="Cron Setup" style="float:none;" /> - This image is for advanced users who wish to set up a cron job for the tasks. This is useful if the board is not accessed often, but you want the tasks to run exactly on time.<br />
<img src="{skin_url}/images/task_run.gif" alt="Run Now" style="float:none;" /> - If this image turns red, it means this task needs to be ran. To run a task, simply click on this icon and it will run the selected task.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>tools_loginauth_</key>
			<title>Login Authentication Manager</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The Login Manager allows you to authenticate your board against an outside user database. Please note this feature is for advanced users. For information on how to use this feature, it is recommended to read the board and developer documentation on the <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=doctor">Documentation</a> page.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>tools_loginauth_login_add</key>
			<title>Login Authentication Manager</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The Login Manager allows you to authenticate your board against an outside user database. Please note this feature is for advanced users. For information on how to use this feature, it is recommended to read the board and developer documentation on the <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=doctor">Documentation</a> page.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>tools_loginauth_login_edit_details</key>
			<title>Login Authentication Manager</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The Login Manager allows you to authenticate your board against an outside user database. Please note this feature is for advanced users. For information on how to use this feature, it is recommended to read the board and developer documentation on the <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=doctor">Documentation</a> page.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>tools_loginauth_login_diagnostics</key>
			<title>Login Authentication Manager</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The Login Manager allows you to authenticate your board against an outside user database. Please note this feature is for advanced users. For information on how to use this feature, it is recommended to read the board and developer documentation on the <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=doctor">Documentation</a> page.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>tools_portal_</key>
			<title>Portal Plug-ins</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[The portal plug-ins are modules that control what is seen on the <a href="{base_url}&section=tools&act=op&code=findsetting&key=ipbportal">IPB Portal</a> page. You can edit the settings for each plug-in by clicking the drop-down to the right of each one.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>tools_postoffice_</key>
			<title><![CDATA[Previous & Current Bulk Emails]]></title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This page allows you to view any past and current bulk emails. You can resend any previous ones, and check the status of ones that are currently being sent. To send a new bulk email, simply click the <i>Create New Email</i> link in the menu to the left of this page.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_group_doadd</key>
			<title>User Groups</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[User Grouping is a quick and powerful way to organize your members. There are 4 preset groups that you cannot remove (Validating, Guest, Member and Admin) although you may edit these at will. A good example of user grouping is to set up a group called 'Moderators' and allow them access to certain forums other groups do not have access to.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_group_dodelete</key>
			<title>User Groups</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[User Grouping is a quick and powerful way to organize your members. There are 4 preset groups that you cannot remove (Validating, Guest, Member and Admin) although you may edit these at will. A good example of user grouping is to set up a group called 'Moderators' and allow them access to certain forums other groups do not have access to.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_group_delete</key>
			<title>Deleting a User Group</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[<b>Note</b>: There is NO UNDO for this. If you delete the group, the only way to get it back it is to recreate the group and move all the members back into it one by one.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>tools_rebuild_</key>
			<title><![CDATA[Recounting & Rebuilding]]></title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Please read each description carefully. Some tools are resource intensive, while others have no way to undo the changes made. Tools such as <i>Rebuild Post Content</i> may take a long time to complete - please be patient and do not close the window until it is completed.<br />
<b>Rebuild Post Content</b> is useful if you recently upgraded your board and certain elements are not showing correctly. If your BBCode, emoticons, or formatting is not showing up correctly, you may want to consider running this tool.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>tools_help_</key>
			<title>Board Help Files</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Help Files are displayed to your users when they click the <i>Help</i> link in the board header. The articles cover basic usage of the default board. If you have common questions or areas that need clarification, you can add your own articles here for your users to view.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>tools_op_</key>
			<title>System Settings</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[System Settings is the main control center for how your board operates. The Settings are grouped together in Setting Groups. You can see the Setting Groups lower down this page, in the same column. For altering a specific setting, you can search for it using the search box to the right of the title bar, just below this box.<br />
Each Setting Group may have a help box for it. Also remember to click the help icon next to specific settings (<img src="{skin_url}/images/about.png" alt="!" style="float:none;" />) for more information on the use of that setting.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>settinggroup_cookies</key>
			<title>Having Trouble Staying Logged In?</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Cookies are stored on each user's computer, and helps them stay logged in after they have left the board. For help on what to enter for the settings, click the help icon next to the settings. If your users are having trouble staying logged in, please check:<br />
<b>Create a stronghold auto-log in cookie?</b> - As noted in the setting description, this enhances the security of your cookies. But it can also cause issues with users who have dynamic IP addresses. You may wish to turn this off to see if this helps the users stay logged in.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>settinggroup_cpusaving</key>
			<title>Have a busy forum? Forum running slow?</title>
			<helptext>This is the section to help improve the performance of your board. Please read through each setting carefully, and adjust them accordingly.</helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>settinggroup_log_prune</key>
			<title>Pruning Board Logs</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Logging is enabled by default in many areas. When logging is enabled, it can take up a large amount of database storage space. It is recommended to enable log pruning of any logs you do not view as important to your board's record keeping.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>settinggroup_ipbportal</key>
			<title>Making Portal The Front Page</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[To do this, you need to edit a single PHP file for your board. <b>If you are not comfortable doing this, we urge you to <a href="{base_url}&section=help&act=support&code=support">submit a ticket</a> for assistance.</b><br /><br />
Find the file <i>init.php</i> in the root directory of your forum. Open it in a text editor and find the line:<br />
<i><b>define( 'IPB_MAKE_PORTAL_HOMEPAGE', 0 );</b></i><br /><br />
Change it to:<br />
<i><b>define( 'IPB_MAKE_PORTAL_HOMEPAGE', 1 );</b></i>
<br /><br />
Save this file and reupload it to your board. Your IPB Portal will now be the front page of your board.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>settinggroup_securityandprivacy</key>
			<title>Security Settings</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[Security is a vital part of your forum. Please take special note to for each setting on this page. Also be sure to click the extra help icon next to specific settings.<br />
<br />
This setting group helps you control member validation, spam bots, and other security/privacy features.<br />If you are still unsure after reading the setting description and optional help text, it is best to leave the setting to whatever the default is.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>content_attach_attach_edit</key>
			<title>Attachment Mini-Image</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This image will need to be stored in:<br />
/style_images/<i>{imgdir}</i>/folder_mime_types/<br/><br/>
For example, the information you would enter would be: <i>folder_mime_types/music.gif</i><br />
Be sure this image is uploaded for each one of your custom image sets.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>

		<helpsections>
			<key>components_idm_show</key>
			<title>IP.Downloads</title>
			<helptext><![CDATA[This is a separate product designed to plug directly into your IP.Board. It offers your users an option to share files. You can create different categories for files to be posted into, allowing one place to upload, download, and share all types of files. To purchase, please contact our Sales Team. If you have already purchased this product and would like IPS to install it for you, please create a new Support Ticket.]]></helptext>
		</helpsections>
	</helpsectionsgroup>

</helpsectionsexport>